You eat well and take medicine well
你好好吃饭好好吃药
Get well early
早点把身体养好
You can't delay your own work
可不能耽误了自己的工作才行
Hello
喂
Jade dew
玉露啊
How are you doing outside all these years
这些年自己在外面过得还顺利吗
Tell our old classmates what you have
有什么就跟我们老同学讲啊
Don't hold on to yourself
不要自己硬撑着
It is
就是的
I asked my husband to introduce you to someone
我让我老公也给你介绍对象啊
It's our age, huh
就是咱们这个年纪哈
Don't ask for looks and marriage history
对长相和婚史就别要求了
You are too demanding since you were a child
你呀就是从小要求太高
How do you do, Miss Lin? You're here
您好 林小姐你来了
You are a distinguished guest of our boss
您是我们老板的贵客
He told you to be sure to entertain you
他吩咐过一定要给您招待好了
Hey, isn't this BMW our car
哎这辆宝马不是我们家那辆车吗
Really
真是的
I told my husband not to pick me up
我都跟我老公说了不要来接我了
This is my boss
这是我老板
It's just the boss
只是老板
That's all
仅此而已
That's not it
那不然呢
A blind date who doesn't belong to our family
跟我们门不当户不对的相亲对象
Thank you today
今天谢谢你啊
But I don't think I need money
不过我不觉得我需要用钱
Stay up in front of the students
在同学们面前撑场面
What I am is what I am
我是什么样就是什么样
I'm not gonna let their values
我不会因为她们的价值观
And belittle myself
而贬低我自己
I didn't belittle you
我没有贬低你的
I'll call you for the meal
饭钱我会打给你
But please don't do this again in the future
但是以后请不要再这样
And
还有
What I promised you
答应你的事
That's it
就到此为止
I have my own business to do
我还有自己的事情要忙
I will go on a blind date with others from tomorrow
明天开始我会去跟别人相亲
I'll find a way over there
蒋家那边我会想办法
I disagree
我不同意
Is my mother's condition getting worse
我妈的病情恶化了吗
I'll book a ticket back for tomorrow
我订明天的票回去
Supplementary recording of Yulu aunt's lines: Your mother told me that the most regrettable thing is to bring you up alone
玉露姨台词补录：你妈跟我说最遗憾的就是独自带大你
Yu Lu Yi's lines are supplemented: but I can't see you get happiness
玉露姨台词补录：却没能看你得到幸福
Supplementary recording of Yulu's lines: That's why I spent so much money to find a blind date agency for you
玉露姨台词补录：所以才花那么多钱给你找相亲中介
I see
我知道了
Supplementary Record of Yulu's Lines: Return Your Clothes
玉露台词补录：衣服还你
This one loves sports
这位啊爱好体育运动
Play volleyball every day
天天打排球
Visual estimation of height is less than 1.9 meters
目测估计身高也就不到1米9
My brother introduces you
哥哥给你介绍
I understand that the height is not written to 1.8 meters
懂了身高没写到1米8
It's only 1.6 meters
就只有1米6
I hope to have a child of my own this year
我呢希望今年能有一个自己的孩子
Give my mother an account
给我妈一交代
Don't worry about watching the children
看孩子的事你不用管
Mom living with us will not tire you
妈跟咱一块住保证累不着你
You are dressed so exquisitely
你这打扮的这么精致
Should be very particular about it
应该挺讲究吧
Girls
女孩子啊
Don't pay attention to these unrealistic things
不要讲究这些不切实际的
Don't dare to worship money
可不敢拜金啊
Thank you for coming out with me
谢谢你陪我出来呀
Miss Jiang is polite
蒋小姐客气了
Accompanying clients is what I should do
陪客户本来就是我应该做的
I just don't know
只是我不知道
When we go to the cinema to read the materials,
我们要到电影院看资料时
You don't really believe what I said, do you
你不会真信我说的话了吧
Or are you pretending to understand and pretend to be confused
还是你揣着明白装糊涂
Or say
还是说
You also think reading information is a good excuse
你也觉得看资料是个不错的借口
I choose c
我选c
I want to buy an ice cream
我想去买个冰淇淋
I'll buy it
我去买吧
Hey
哎
You pick up the ticket first
你先去取票
It's too late to wait
等会来不及
Good
好
Nanfeng
楠枫
This is the only flavor left
只有这一个口味了
Let's eat together
一起吃吧
Well, I'll go to the bathroom.
那个我去上个厕所啊
Good
好
Would you like to try some coffee, Miss Lin
林小姐尝尝咖啡吧
What would you like to eat tonight
今天晚上想吃点什么呀
Jin Feng is next to me, too
津枫也在我旁边呢
Why don't you ask Miss Lin and the four of us to eat together
要不你叫林小姐我们四个一起去吃
Ah, Miss Lin went on a blind date
啊林小姐相亲去了
Xu Jinfeng's Supplementary Record: Walking Home
徐津枫补录：走了 回家
What I promised you
答应你的事
Let's call it a day
就到此为止吧
I have my own business to do
我还有自己的事情要忙
I will go on a blind date with others from tomorrow
明天开始我会去跟别人相亲
Let's cancel the contract
我们解除合约吧